All right, you're done. Lets look at the
solution. We'll begin by adding a log tag
into our abstract threaded SyncAdapter. Since this stuff
runs in the background, it's really helpful to have
some logging. Since we ultimately want to run
the SyncAdapter in undetected mode. Let's pull the location
query from our utility class. And then we
paste in the code from our existing sunshine service.
We'll have to patch a few things up. We'll have to call getContext to
get the current context, for example. Note that I copied over ad location at
the same time I copied over the primary function. And then finally, we'll fix
update weather to use the new helper
function in our SyncAdapter. Let's run this.